tell you some things about me I like
guns I'm a gun person all right Utah
don't mess with me okay listen we're
safe okay we're good
no here's the thing I like guns right I
I live in LA now and when people hear
their hear me say I like guns they don't
hear me say I like guns what they hear
is stuff at Yosemite Sam's why they like
[Laughter]
I I think all women should have a gun
right I think all of us should we've run
out of bad guys really quickly right and
I believe in the second man I think most
people should be able to have a good
right not everybody right like if
someone had a gun to my head I believe
me not this guy
[Laughter]
something else I like ghosts yeah
there's one ghost somebody here I mean
I'm into ghosts like hardcore I when I'm
on the road I like to go and like go do
like ghost tours and stuff I was I was
on the road recently guy goes hey man
you want to come check out my haunted
artifact collection I was like yes yes I
do
so it's true sorry we go in there there
we go in there and it's just a room with
hundreds of dolls and then he goes this
doll is haunted isn't that creepy I was
like that's the least creepy thing about
this whole situation
I was in Gettysburg I was walking around
this guy comes up to me goes yo dawg you
wanna go on a ghost tour I was like sure
white guy with dress let's do this so
we're going and here's the thing about
getting Berg everything is haunted
apparently right he was like the Oprah
Winfrey of ghost tours he's just like
that place is haunted that place is
haunted you'll get a ghost you get a
ghost I'm pretty sure he's making stuff
up cuz he's like that 7-eleven is
haunted by the ghost of Colonel Sanders
that's not well we get we get finished
right and he goes hey listen you want to
go to the haunted bridge was like yes
yes I do because alright we go this
haunted bridge you go I say how how was
it hard to tell me the story and he says
100 years ago Indian lady jumped off a
bridge now she haunts you ooh spooky and
I asked him I said how do you know it's
haunted and he said I quote and I quote
he said because sometimes when I'm
standing on the bridge I can feel a cold
breeze
that's it that's the whole reasoning
that he's not he's just afraid of cold
breezes y'all that's hey hey man you
wanna go to Chicago
oh the Windy City no man that place is
haunted be like hey white guy with
dreads it's kind of hot in here can we
put on the a/c
you mean ghost conditioning
hey did you know Drybar company has
their own app download it now to watch
my whole special